Kheel, Theodore W. Arbitration files 6021/003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- TWU Local 100 (Ben Ingram et al.) and Liberty Coaches, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- TWU Local 100 and liberty Coaches, Inc., 1982 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- TWU Local 100 (Shelia Sands) and Liberty Coaches, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- TWU Local 100 (Charles Perry) and Liberty Coaches, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- TWU Local 100 (Walter Brown, et al.) and Liberty Coaches, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- TWU Local 100 and liberty coaches, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- TWU Local 100 (Stuart Zuckerman) and Liberty Coaches, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- TWU Local 100 (John Moore) and Liberty Coaches, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- TWU Local 100 (Willie McMiller) and Liberty Lines, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  July 31 - Nov 6
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Lines, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  Jan 26 - Feb 14
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Lines, Inc., 1983 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- TWU Local 100 (Hopeton Matthews) and Liberty Lines, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  March 22, 1983 - Jan 12, 1984
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Lines, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  June 27 - Nov 23
- TWU 100 (John Viviano) and Liberty Lines Airport Services, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- TWU Local 100 (Bernard Carrion, et al.) and Liberty Lines Express, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- TWU Local 100 (Richard Reilly, et al.) and Liberty Lines Express, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  March 20
- TWU Local 100 (Raymond Delarosa) and Liberty Lines Express, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- TWU Local 100 (Calvin Cutterno, et al.) and Liberty Lines Express, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- TWU Local 100 (Floyd McIver, et al.) and Liberty Lines Express, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Lines Express, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- TWU Local 100 (Charles Roberts) and Liberty Lines Express, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- TWU Local 100 (James Perez) and Liberty Lines Express, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- TWU Local 100 (Jose Pina) and Liberty Lines Express, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  June 10
- TWU Local 100 (Don Alacci) and Liberty Lines Express, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- TWU Local 100 (John Reed) and Liberty Lines Express, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- TWU Local 100 (Richard Spergel) and Liberty Lines Express, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- TWU Local 100 (James Perez) and Liberty Lines Express, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  Sept 16
- TWU Local 100 (Richard D'Ambrosio, et al.) and Liberty Lines Express, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  Sept 25
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Lines Express, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- TWU Local 100 (Cecily Gomes) and Liberty Lines Express, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Jan 13
- TWU Local 100 (Dennis Droesch) and Liberty Lines Express, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Feb 11
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Lines Express, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- TWU Local 100 (Herman Battle) and Liberty Lines Express, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  Aug 20
- TWU Local 100 (Mario Gallo) and Liberty Lines Express, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Nov 18
- TWU Local 100 (Donald D'Intino et al.) and Liberty Lines Express, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- TWU Local 100 (Davis Jackson, et al.) and Liberty Lines Express, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- TWU Local 100 (Pedro Antunes, et al.) and Liberty Lines Express, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  Nov 26
- TWU Local 100 (Anthony Oddo) and Liberty Lines Express, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  Feb 22
- TWU Local 100 (Stuart Zuckerman) and Liberty Lines Express, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  Feb 24
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Lines Express, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- TWU Local 100 (Goolcharan Harnanan) and Liberty Lines Express, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- TWU Local 100 (Deloris Carver) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- TWU Local 100 (Ronald Wilkins) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- TWU Local 100 (Sergio Rosario) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  Nov 8
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Lines Transit, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  Nov 25
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Lines Transit, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  Dec 5
- TWU Local 100 (James Perez) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  Dec 26, 1985 - Feb 3, 1986
- TWU Local 100 (Anne Williams) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  Dec 26
- TWU Local 100 (Rene Mirand) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- TWU Local 100 (Seamus Roche) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- TWU Local 100 (Walter Sautos) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Feb 3
- TWU Local 100 (William Young) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- TWU Local 100 (Paul Denault, et al.) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  April 21
- TWU Local 100 (Roland Anderson) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- TWU Local 100 (Raul Vasquez) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- TWU Local 100 (Eric Williams)and Liberty Lines Transit, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- TWU Local 100 (Paul Denault) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- TWU Local 100 (Peter Dingman) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- TWU Local 100 (Ernesto Homs) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Aug 21
- TWU Local 100 (Rose Casucci, et al.) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- TWU Local 100 (Jorge Morais) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- TWU Local 100 (Theodore Foster) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Dec 31
- TWU Local 100 (Von Simmons) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- TWU Local 100 (Malcolm Quick) and Liberty Lines Transit, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- TWU Local 100 (Irving Ives) and MABSTOA, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- TWU Local 100 (David Williams) and MABSTOA, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- TWU Local 100 (Alfred Sunderland) and MABSTOA, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  June 24, 1963 - June 24, 1964
- TWU Local 100 (Patrick Kennedy) and MABSTOA, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- TWU Local 100 (Gerard Cunningham, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Sept 24
- TWU Local 100 (Charles Cala) and MABSTOA, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- TWU Local 100 (Abe Sakowsky) and MABSTOA, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  Oct 4
- TWU Local 100 (Clarence Smith) and MABSTOA, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- TWU Local 100 (John Carney) and MABSTOA, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  Jan 31, 1964 - Jan 13, 1965
- TWU Local 100 (William Lyons) and MABSTOA, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  March 25, 1964 - March 18, 1965
- TWU Local 100 (Lawrence Coleman et al.) and MABSTOA, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  March 30
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  April 3
- TWU Local 100 (Walter Schneider et al.) and MABSTOA, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- TWU Local 100 (Ernest Cosentino) and MABSTOA, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- TWU Local 100 (Angelo Cohen) and MABSTOA, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- TWU Local 100 (Richard Hughes) and MABSTOA, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- TWU Local 100 (James Cahillane, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  Sept 28
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  Nov 2
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  Dec 16
- TWU Local 100 (J. Kiely) and MABSTOA, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  Feb 17
- TWU Local 100 (John Luker, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- TWU Local 100 (Richard Hughes, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- TWU Local 100 (Dennis Adams)and MABSTOA, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  June 23
- TWU Local 100 (John McCarthy, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- TWU Local 100 (Richard Slutsky, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1966-1982 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  March 3, 1966 - April 21, 1982
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  March 25
- TWU Local 100 (Armando Muti, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- TWU Local 100 (James Payne) and MABSTOA, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- TWU Local 100 (Michael Twomey, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- TWU Local 100 (Philip Redmond) and MABSTOA, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- TWU Local 100 (James Mactiernan) and MABSTOA, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- TWU Local 100 (William James, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  Jan 25
- TWU Local 100 (John Welsh, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  Feb 14
- TWU Local 100 (William Jones, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  April 20
- TWU Local 100 (George Beattie) and MABSTOA, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- TWU Local 100 (Morris Greenblatt) and MABSTOA, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  May 31
- TWU Local 100 (John Alyward, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  June 15
- TWU Local 100 (R. Caravano, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- TWU Local 100 (Nicholas D'Apice) and MABSTOA, 1967-1975 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  July 31, 1967 - Feb 26, 1975
- TWU Local 100 (Lawrence Martin, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  Sept 1
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- TWU Local 100 (Michael Daly) and MABSTOA, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  Nov 28
- TWU Local 100 (Anthony DiMauro, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  Feb 7
- TWU Local 100 (Joseph Dunst, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- TWU Local 100 ( Anthony De Losa, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- TWU Local 100 (Martin Milk) and MABSTOA, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  June 7
- TWU Local 100 (Maurice Walsh, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  Aug 23
- TWU Local 100 (Harry Beattie, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- TWU Local 100 (Alan Halyberg, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 57)
- TWU Local 100 (Edward Finn, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  Feb 28
- TWU Local 100 (Artist McKenzie, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 59)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA - Charles Roberts, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  April 16, 1969 - Jan 19, 1971
- TWU Local 100 (Jesse Baity, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 61)
- TWU Local 100 (Albert Health, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 62)
- TWU Local 100 (Robert Spencer) and MABSTOA, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 63)
- TWU Local 100 (Arnold Abernathy) and MABSTOA, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 64)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 65)
- TWU Local 100 (F. Cohen, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 66)
- TWU Local 100 (Sterling Tanks) and MABSTOA, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  Dec 18
- TWU Local 100 (Edward Hawthorne) and MABSTOA, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  March 13
- TWU Local 100 (Theodore Cohen, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 69)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA - Henry Thomas, et al., 1970 (Box 11, Folder 70)
- TWU Local 100 (Jimmy Bennett) and MABSTOA, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 71)
- TWU Local 100 (Joseph McMillan) and MABSTOA, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 72)
- TWU Local 100 (Robert Stoker) and MABSTOA, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  Feb 23 - Nov 2
- TWU Local 100 (T Gaffney) and MABSTOA, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 74)
- TWU Local 100 (Ralph Home, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 75)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  May 11
- TWU Local 100 (Henry Lopez, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  July 6, 1972 - June 25, 1973
- TWU Local 100 (Randolph Harper, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  Sept 7
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA - Joseph Coles, et al., 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  Nov 8, 1972 - June 4, 1974
- TWU Local 100 (John Murphy, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 80)
- TWU Local 100 (S. Castellano) and MABSTOA, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  April 11
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA - James Donald Parris, et al., 1973 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  April 11 - Nov 5
- TWU Local 100 (Profirio Santos) and MABSTOA, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 83)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA - Thomas McTigue, et al., 1974 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  Jan 4 - Oct 22
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA - Christopher Quinliven, et al., 1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Jan 6 - Dec 5
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Feb 9 - Aug 29
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Jan 14 - Dec 14
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA Osborne Wright, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  April 7 - June 16
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA - Allen Rothenberg, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  April 22 - May 24
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA - Vincent Barrett, et al., 1978 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  July 20 - Dec 22
- TWU Local 100 (Charles Mills) and MABSTOA, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- TWU Local 100 (B Wright) and MABSTOA, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  March 17
- TWU Local 100 (Adrian De Roo, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- TWU Local 100 (Gonzolo Gomez, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- TWU Local 100 (June Haste) and MABSTOA, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- TWU Local 100 (James Murray, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- TWU Local 100 (M. Azala, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- TWU Local 100 (Roger Zanco) and MABSTOA, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- TWU Local 100 (Donald McCain, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- TWU Local 100 (Willie Morrison) and MABSTOA, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- TWU Local 100 (Ira Beskin, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA - A. Ponce, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- TWU Local 100 (M. Fitzpatrick, et al.) and MABSTOA, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- TWU Local 100 (John English) and MABSTOA, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  July 25
- TWU Local 100 (L.C. Brown) and MABSTOA, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  Aug 31 - Sept 1
- TWU Local 100 (Willie Gholsen) and MABSTOA, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA - Thomas Hubbard, et al., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- TWU Local 100 (Frank Cincinnati) and MABSTOA, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- TWU Local 100 (Daniel Flores) and MABSTOA, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- TWU Local 100 (John Pezza) and MABSTOA, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- TWU Local 100 (Joaquin Conceicao) and National Custom Van Corp., 1985 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- TWU Local 100 (Donald Brower) and NY Bus Service, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- TWU Local 100 (Edward Daniels) and NY Bus Service, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- TWU Local 100 (Theodore Pritchard, et al.) and NY Bus Service, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- TWU Local 100 (Kyaiakos Potossis) and NY Bus Service, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- TWU Local 100 (Egbert Goldborne) and NY Bus Service, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- TWU Local 100 (Victor Navedo) and NY Bus Service, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- TWU Local 100 (Katherine McDee) and NY Bus Service, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- TWU Local 100 (Vincent Maya) and NY Bus Service (Box 12, Folder 39)
- TWU Local 100 (Jose Mercado) and NY Bus Service, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- TWU Local 100 (Louis Torres) and NY Bus Service, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- TWU Local 100 (Ricaros Thompson) and NY Bus Service, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- TWU Local 100 (Daniel Scovotti, et al.) and NY Bus Service, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  May 20. 1977 - Feb 1, 1978
- TWU Local 100 and NY Bus Service, 1977-1982 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  Nov 7, 1977 - May 18, 1982
- TWU Local 100 (James Normoyle) and NY Bus Service, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  Jan 6, 1978 - Feb 1, 1979
- TWU Local 100 (Patricia Keenan) and NY Bus Service, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  March 28
- TWU Local 100 (James Byrne, et al.) and NY Bus Service, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- TWU Local 100 (Rosaline Soracino, et al.) and NY Bus Service, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  June 28
- TWU Local 100 and NY Bus Service/Town, 1979-1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Oct 18, 1979 - June 25, 1992
- TWU Local 100 (Elberta Melville) and NY Bus Service, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- TWU Local 100 and NY Bus Service - Daniel Riordin, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- TWU Local 100 and NY Bus Service, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- TWU Local 100 (Sophia Pignataro) and NY Bus Service, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- TWU Local 100 and NY Bus Service, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- TWU Local 100 (Anthony Russo, et al.) and NY Bus Service, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- TWU Local 100 (Robin Wendell) and New York Bus Service, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- TWU Local 100 (Claudio Smith, et al.) and NY Bus Service, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- TWU Local 100 (Adolph Eaddy, et al.) and NY Bus Service, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- TWU Local 100 (John Bolan, et al.) and NY Bus Service, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- TWU Local 100 (George Chin) and NY Bus Service, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- TWU Local 100 and New York Bus Service - Clayton Spruill, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- TWU Local 100 (Anthony Navarra, et al.) and NY Bus Service, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- TWU Local 100 (Richardo Thomas) and NY Bus Service, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- TWU Local 100 (Karl Huber) and NY Bus Service, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- TWU Local 100 (Robert Taylor) and NY Bus Service, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- TWU Local 100 (Franklin Nelson) and NY Bus Service, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- TWU Local 100 (Eric Rowe, et al.) and NY Bus Service, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- TWU Local 100 (Jenny Potter) and NY Bus Service, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- TWU Local 100 (Lawrence Davis) and NY Bus Service, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- TWU Local 100 (Manuel Torres) and NY Bus Service, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- TWU Local 100 (Keith Blackwood, et al.) and NY Bus Service, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- TWU Local 100 (Joseph Venturini) and NY Bus Service, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- TWU Local 100 (Camille Narvaez, et al.) and NY Bus Service, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- TWU Local 100 and New York Bus Service, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  Nov 1 - Feb 22
- TWU Local 100 (Douglas Hesselbarth) and NY Bus Service, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- TWU Local 100 (William Wasilewski, et al.) and NY Bus Service, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  April 25 - June 6
- TWU Local 100 and NY Bus Service, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- TWU Local 100 (James Vairo, et al.) and NY Bus Town, 1970-1982 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  June 6, 1970 - Dec 28, 1982
- Transport Workers Union of America, CIO Local 100 and NYC Omnibus Corporation Denis McCarthy, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Transport Workers Union of America, CIO and New York City Transit Authority, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Transport Workers Union of America, CIO and NYC Transit Authority, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  Oct 10
- Transport Workers Union Local 100 and New York City transit Authority, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Transport Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO and NYC Transit Authority, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Transport Workers of America and TWU Local 100 and NYC Transit Authority, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- TWU Local 100 and NYCTA Folder 1 of 2, 1959-1974 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  June 12, 1959 - Oct 3, 1974
- TWU Local 100 and MABSTOA - James O'Reilly, et al., 1979 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  Feb 15 - Aug 28
- TWU Local 100 and NY Bus Service, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  Mar 22
- TWU Local 100 and NY Bus Service, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- TWU Local 100 (Roy Cuthbert) and NY Bus Service, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Transport Workers Union of America AFL-CIO Local 100 and New York City Transit Authority, 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Transport Workers Union of America AFL-CIO Local 100 and New York City Transit Authority, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Transport Workers Union of America Local 100 AFL-CIO and New York City Transit Authority, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Transport Workers Union of America AFL-CIO Local 100 and New York City Transit Authority, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Transport Workers Union of America and TWU Local 100 and NYC Transit Authority, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Transport Workers Union of America Local 100 AFL-CIO and New York City Transit Authority, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Transport workers Union of America local 100 AFL-CIO and New York city Authority, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Local 100, TWU and NYC Transit Authority, Edward Frazer, et al., 1980 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- TWU Local 100 and NYCTA Folder 2 of 2, 1959-1962 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  June 12, 1959 - Dec 28, 1962
- Transport Workers Union, Local 100 and NYCTA, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  Dec 23
- TWU Local 100 and NYCTA, 1977-1981 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  Nov 7, 1977 - Sept 24, 1981
- TWU Local 100 and NYCTA, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- TWU Local 100 (Edward Washington, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  Jan 13 - Dec 8
- TWU Local 100 ( Walter Joyman, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981-1987 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  Jan 20, 1981 - Aug 19, 1987
- TWU Local 100 (Martin Ostrofsky, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  Jan 30 - Nov 6
- TWU Local 100 Robert Rhemus, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  Feb 9 - Oct 7
- TWU Local 100 and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- TWU Local 100 (John Lewis) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- TWU Local 100 (Margaret Brunson, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- TWU Local 100 (Joan Bater, et al.), 1981 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  March 23
- TWU Local 100 (Arthur Shapiro, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  March 26 - April 7
- TWU Local 100 (Richard Russo, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- TWU Local 100 (Willis Gaynor) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- TWU Local 100 (Joseph Houghton, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  April 7 - July 9
- TWU Local 100 (Marie Clemente) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- TWU Local 100 (Arlene Woodson, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- TWU Local 100 (Rafael Russo) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  May 15
- TWU local 100 (Lois Thames, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  May 18
- TWU Local 100 (R. Stroman) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- TWU Local 100 (Eugene Rhodes, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- TWU Local 100 (Dominick Filocomo, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  May 29 - Dec 24
- TWU Local 100 (Joseph Morelli, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  May 29, 1981 - April 23, 1982
- TWU Local 100 (Barbara Graham) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- TWU Local 100 (Edward DeLuca) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- TWU local 100 (Raymond Lachapelle, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- TWU Local 100 (Hasher Edmonds, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  July 2
- TWU Local 100 (Edward Brown) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  July 7 - Oct 21
- TWU Local 100 (Lubomir Ondracek, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  July 17 - Sept 2
- TWU Local 100 (Lester Savarese, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  July 22 - Dec 2
- TWU Local 100 and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- TWU Local 100 (Lance Colbey, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- TWU Local 100 (Antonio Alcamo) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- TWU Local 100 and NYCTA - John Anders, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- TWU Local 100 (George Salis, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Sept 24 - Oct 15
- TWU Local 100 (Michael Silverman, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  Sept 30, 1981 - May 20, 1982
- TWU Local 100 (Reginald Brunett) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- TWU Local 100 and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- TWU Local 100 (John Carrion, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- TWU Local 100 (Max Beltran, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- TWU Local 100 (James Jones, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- TWU Local 100 and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- TWU Local 100 and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- TWU Local 100 (Floretta Bowser, et al.) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  Jan 21
- TWU Local 100 and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- TWU Local 100 (Antonio Ruggiero, et al.) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- TWU Local 100 (Leslie Lubin) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  Jan 20